<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Group Project</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Kenkōtchi</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_stats">Stats</string>
    <string name="title_map">Map</string>
    <string name="title_quiz">Quiz</string>

    <string name="maps_api_key">AIzaSyBi50vULcwsdebpsILZxQ9lyX6L6Oxc3kA</string>

    <string name="question_instructions">For each of the following questions rate yourself from one to five, one being on the left and five being on the right</string>
    <string name="question_1">Little interest or pleasure in doing things</string>
    <string name="question_2">Feeling down, depressed, or hopeless</string>
    <string name="question_3">Trouble falling or staying asleep, or sleeping too much</string>
    <string name="question_4">Feeling tired or having little energy</string>
    <string name="question_5">Poor appetite or overeating </string>
    <string name="question_6">Feeling bad about yourself or that you are a failure or have let yourself or your family down</string>
    <string name="question_7">Trouble concentrating on things, such as reading the newspaper or watching television</string>
    <string name="question_8">Moving or speaking so slowly that other people could have noticed. Or the opposite being so fidgety or restless that you have been moving around a lot more than usual</string>
    <string name="question_9">Thoughts that you would be better off dead, or of hurting yourself</string>
    <string name="question_10">How close are you to getting the recommended daily water intake? (The recommended water intake for a man is 15 cups, 11 for a woman)</string>
    <string name="question_11">How would you rate your activity for today</string>
    <string name="question_12">How close do you think you are to the recommended hours of sleep (Recommended hours of sleep (for ages 13–18) 8–10 hours, ( for ages 18++) 7++ hours)</string>
    <string name="question_13">How would you rate your eating consistency? </string>
    <string name="question_14">How many servings of fruits/veggies have you had today? </string>

    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>

    <string name="mental_desc">Indicator of how you are feeling emotionally—overwhelmed, burdened, hopeless, etc</string>
    <string name="eating_desc">Indicator of your eating habits—over or under-eating, eating irregularly, or lacking nutrition</string>
    <string name="stress_desc">Indicator of stress based on answers to questions about life commitments like school and work</string>
    <string name="screen_desc">Measurement of how beneficial your screen time is for your mental and physical health</string>
    <string name="water_desc">How is your daily water consumption?</string>
    <string name="fitness_desc">Are you getting a healthy level of physical activity?</string>
    <string name="sleep_desc">Are you getting an adequate amount of sleep every night?</string>

</resources>